let quiz = [{
        question: "Ratio of difference between the ages of father and son and sum of ages of father and son is 3 : 10. If the difference of the age of father and son is 24 years, then find the age of Father.",
        option: [
            "52 years",
            "80 years",
            "104 years",
            "28 years"
        ],
        answer: 1,
    }, {
        question: "The age of a teacher is 40 years more than the age of a student. The age of one more student who is 8 years elder than the previous student is half of the age of the teacher. Find the age of the second student. ",

        option: [
            "24 years",
            "36 years",
            "32 years",
            "20 years"
        ],
        answer: 3,
    }, {
        question: "The sum of ages of two brothers two years ago was 40 years. The ratio of their ages after four years would be 8: 5. Find their present ages. ",

        option: [
            "24 years and 12 years",
            "32 years and 22 years",
            "36 years and 24 years",
            "28 years and 16 years"
        ],
        answer: 4,
    }, {
        question: "Age of Mohan is 3 times of his son and 4 times of his daughter. Son is 5 year elder than daughter find the age of Mohan?",

        option: [
            "60 years",
            "56 years",
            "48 years",
            "40 years"
        ],
        answer: 1,
    }, {
        question: "The age of teacher is 300% of the age of a student. After four years, the ratio of the ages of the teacher and the student becomes 13 : 5. Find the present age of the teacher.",

        option: [
            "50",
            "20",
            "48",
            "52"
        ],
        answer: 3,
    },


    {
        question: "Tisha said to Roy, the sum of our ages k years ago was 52. The sum of our ages k + 2 years hence will be 108 years. What is the sum of their present ages?",

        option: [
            "76 years",
            "78 years",
            "80 years",
            "823 years"
        ],
        answer: 2,
    }, {
        question: "Age of Ravi is 5 times of his son, after 15 years the ratio of age of Ravi and son is 13 : 5, find the age of Ravi?",

        option: [
            "50 years",
            "60 years",
            "90 years",
            "78 years"
        ],
        answer: 1,
    }, {
        question: "6 years ago age of A and B are in the ratio of 7 : 10. 10 years after the sum of ages A and B is 100 years. C is 12 years elder than B. Find the present age of C.",

        option: [
            "39 years",
            "28 years",
            "58 years",
            "42 years"
        ],
        answer: 3,
    }, {
        question: "The ratio between the present age of two friends Arvind and Mahesh is 5 : 6. After 8 years the ratio of their ages will be 7 : 8. Find the sum of Arvind and Mahesh's ages after 10 years.",

        option: [
            "45",
            "60",
            "64",
            "74"
        ],
        answer: 3,
    }, {
        question: "Age of A is 1.5 times of B. The ratio of their ages after 10 years is 4 : 3. then what is the current age of B?",

        option: [
            "15",
            "30",
            "45",
            "20"
        ],
        answer: 4,
    },
];